const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
    {
      question: "ἀδικία",
      answers: ["ongerechtigheid"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ἀλήθεια",
      answers: ["waarheid"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ἁμαρτία",
      answers: ["zonde"],
      explanation: "(hamartologie)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "βασιλεία",
      answers: ["koninkrijk"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "γενεά",
      answers: ["generatie"],
      explanation: "(genealogie)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ἐκκλησία",
      answers: ["vergadering", "kerk"],
      explanation: "(ecclesiologie)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ἐξουσία",
      answers: ["gezag"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ἐπαγγελία",
      answers: ["belofte"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ἡμέρα",
      answers: ["dag"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "θύρα",
      answers: ["deur"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "θυσία",
      answers: ["slachtoffer"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "καρδια",
      answers: ["hart"],
      explanation: "(cardiografie, cardioloog)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "μαρτυρία",
      answers: ["getuigenis"],
      explanation: "(martelaar)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "μετάνοια",
      answers: ["berouw"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "οἰκια",
      answers: ["huis"],
      explanation: "(economie, econoom)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "παρουσία",
      answers: ["komst"],
      explanation: "(parousie)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "πέτρα",
      answers: ["rots"],
      explanation: "(Petrus)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "σοφία",
      answers: ["wijsheid"],
      explanation: "(filosofie, Sofie)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "σωτηρία",
      answers: ["heil", "redding"],
      explanation: "(soteriologie)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "χαρά",
      answers: ["vreugde"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "χήρα",
      answers: ["weduwe"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "χρεία",
      answers: ["behoefte"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ὥρα",
      answers: ["uur"],
      explanation: "(horloge)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "Γαλιλαία",
      answers: ["Galilea"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "Ἰουδαία",
      answers: ["Judea"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "γλῶσσα",
      answers: ["tong"],
      explanation: "(glossolalie)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "δόξα",
      answers: ["glorie", "heerlijkheid"],
      explanation: "(doxologie)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "θάλασσα",
      answers: ["zee"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "Παῦλος",
      answers: ["Paulus"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "Πέτρος",
      answers: ["Petrus"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    }
]
const lesson9Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson9-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 9 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson9Vocabulary